Time for another wig.
First of all, I don't even know whose
company.
Now, the previous ones I've done, it's
come from a particular wig company
because the box or the packaging will
say so.
This case
I don't know.
So, we're going to learn together. Once
again, those who know me know I will buy
it, set it to the side, and literally
forget what I bought.
And I won't go back to the TikTok shop
to see cuz I want to be surprised,
right? So, just know I'll link it.
So, let's get into it.
I don't know the style. I don't know the
manufacturer.
Uh, the packaging just says it's made
somewhere not in this country, okay?
And uh, affordable because
you get the bag,
you get the wig, okay? No clippy
clippies, no cappies, just
take this hair and shut up. That's what
they said. All right, I get you.
Did I get
Okay.
Stay focused, Tracy. Stay focused.
>> [snorts]
>> Um, first and foremost, I am not going
to go trim this one or anything, but do
know this one is asking for some work
because it is a full frontal, okay? So,
what I'm going to do is I'm going to try
it on al dente
with the frontal hanging out. I'll post
a picture at the end of the video so you
can see what it looks like once I
clipped it up and it's on me. But, we
just going to go in. We're just going to
go in.
First of all,
these type, again, once I link it,
you'll know who they are. I bought
another wig from them. When I tell you
it is a good quality wig, but the only
downside is how thick
these are. See how thick this is? So,
you really have to make sure you secure
this because it can be a lot of
movement.
It did bother me at first when I got
another wig that had this, but then I
understood. When it's this thick, they
actually can put more intention into how
it's made. It has like a different type
of a quality to it. Right? They
literally are being very intentional
about how these are split up. Some with
the thin the thinner um cap,
they can only do so much.
These, they're very weighty, hence the
thicker scalp. So just know that when
you order this. So if you're a person
who'd be doing hot flashes and you can't
figure out how to control it,
think about that when you get this wig,
okay? Be sure you're taking whatever
vitamin, drinking all the water you need
to drink because it's going to be warm.
All right? So right now I'm just trying
to get the
Why am I struggling? Let me get the
scissors. Hold on. Okay, I've cut it off
cuz it was a little tag. No need in
showing you the tag cuz they don't tell
you who made it either.
Back to what I was saying earlier. So it
is a full frontal meaning you're going
to have to trim it to fit your face and
your style.
It does have the interior
Ah.
Girl, find it.
The combs, which these are a little
further back which works for people with
the receding hairline because you may
braid your hair to a certain point.
These are far enough back where they can
still grip.
And of course,
the band.
And it does This is meant to be able to
like a 360 because as you can see, it
has
the
back.
Drawing a blank. All right, guys. So
let's just see what we have and again,
I'll post a picture later after I cute
it all up, but I'm not going to do that
at this exact moment. I'm just going to
get it on so we can see what I ordered
cuz again, I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. Hook that back there. Come back to
the
Oh, so I'm going to be a problem with
this one. I already know.
I already know cuz again, remember how I
showed you how when they have that
thicker cap, you have more options
because there's really scalp everywhere.
All right, so again, full frontal.
And
child.
Look.
You ain't going to tell me that I didn't
have my hair locked
the other day. That's what you're not
going to do cuz you was a lie.
You was a total lie.
Yes. Yes, ma'am.
I'll be glad to show you guys a picture
after I go and I trim it up and get it
laid down just right. But see how many
Look at this.
I can keep parting.
I can keep splitting.
I can keep going, literally.
Literally.
Because
this type of wig gives you the options.
Yes, it does still has the baby hair
that you can use or lay down once you
cut the edges.
So this is a overall wig.
Y'all know she cute. Shut up.
Shut up.
Okay, well, check that photo.
Cuz that photo was telling the truth.
Yes, I'll have on a different shirt.
But this was really just a Look, I'm
moving it. I'm moving it. I'm twisting
it. I'm going. And I mean, I am
This
is
thick.
This ain't the chintzy ones. This
actually feels like
locks.
Truly, it feels Look at the texture. Can
you see it? There you go.
It is giving locked hair.
It is giving
4 hours later.
It's giving that.
And like I said, it's a 360, so
literally, it is allowing you I'm going
to switch to the back.
Again, I haven't laid it down.
But,
you can go all the way around with this,
y'all.
All the way around.
Pinning it up.
Making it do what it do.
Doing knots in each of the corners.
All the things, okay.
We like her, too, and we shall go I'mma
back up so you can't see the full
frontal as much.
But, you can kind of get the illusion.
Yeah.
Go on and get it.
I think you'll enjoy it and you'll have
fun wearing it.
You will.
Enjoy the photo.